BRAC Additional Records 5488 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 65 (Box 103)
  - Social Security Amendments of 1965: Report of the Committee on Finance, United States Senate (Box 103, Folder 20)
    June 29-30, 1965. Bound.
  - Social Security Amendments of 1965: Report of the Committee on Finance, United States Senate (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Social Security Amendments of 1965: Conference Report (Box 103, Folder 22)
    July 26, 1965. Bound.
  - Social Security Amendments of 1965: Conference Report (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Social Security Amendments of 1965: Conference Report (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - Social Security Amendments of 1965: Conference Report (Box 103, Folder 25)
  - Compilation of the Social Security Laws, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    Through December 31, 1962. Bound.
  - HR 1897, HR 2004, and HR 2331: Bills to Amend the Merchant Marine Act of 1936 as Amended (Box 103, Folder 27)
    March 5-20, 1936. Bound.
  - Social Security Act - General Correspondence, 1954-1967 (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - Social Security Act and Amendments, 1935-1965 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    1935-1965
- 73-176 (Box 104)
  - United States Congress - Lobbyists: Registration, 1970-1973 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    1970-January 1973
  - Work Material for Lobby Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Taft-Hartley Act - Affidavits, 1957-1959 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    August 1957-1959
  - Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1964, 1964-1971 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Surface Transportation Committee (Railroads), 1959-1960 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    February 1959-June 1960. Includes Bound Materials.
  - United States Congress - Urban Mass Transportation Act of 1964, 1964-1972 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    1964-September 29, 1972
  - United States Congress - Rail Passenger Service Act of 1970 (Rail Pax), 1971 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    January 1971-August 31, 1971
  - United States Congress - Rail Passenger Service Act of 1970 (Railpax), 1971-1972 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    September 1971-December 1972
- 144-322-0 (Box 105)
  - Universal Military Training, 1948-1972 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    May 5, 1948-December 1972. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities, International Vice President, 1960-1975 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    1960-May 1975
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Semi-Monthly Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    May 1, 1974-September 1975
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Bi-Monthly Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    December 4, 1973-April 30, 1974
  - Grand Lodge - Data Processing Department, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    May 1972-June 1973
  - General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    March 1975-November 1976
  - General Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    January 1973-February 1975
  - Cincinnati Building File, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    January 1, 1972-December 31, 1973
- 284 - 0-21 (Box 106)
  - State Legislation - Right to Work Laws (Various States), 1961-1971 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Facts - Reference Material, 1960-1969 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - State Legislation - Alabama, 1959-1967 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - State Legislation - Alaska, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    June 7-10, 1961
  - State Legislation - Arkansas, 1947-1970 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - State Legislation - California, 1963-1970 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Legislation - Canada, 1960-1962 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - State Legislation - Arizona, 1955-1969 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - State Legislation - Colorado, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - State Legislation - Connecticut, 1955-1967 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - State Legislation - Delaware, 1959-1970 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - State Legislation - District of Columbia, 1960-1962 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - State Legislation - Florida, 1965-1968 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - State Legislation - Georgia, 1965-1968 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - State Legislation - Idaho, 1956-1970 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - State Legislation - Illinois, 1966-1971 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - State Legislation - Indiana, 1964-1970 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - State Legislation - Iowa, 1958-1966 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - State Legislation - Kansas, 1965-1969 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - State Legislation - Louisiana, 1958-1970 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    May 24, 1958-June 8, 1970
  - State Legislation - Kentucky, 1958-1970 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - State Legislation - Maine, 1961-1969 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - State Legislation - Maine: Public Laws as Enacted by the One Hundred and Second Legislature of the State of Maine, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    January 6, 1965- June 4, 1965. Bound.
  - State Legislation - Maine: Public Laws of the State of Maine, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    Newspaper Format. Laws become effective September 10, 1961.
- 39-52 (Box 107)
  - Compilation of Laws of the State of North Dakota covering the Powers and Duties of the Public Service Commission and Constitutional and Statutory Provisions, 1951 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    Bound. July 1, 1951.
  - State Legislation - North Dakota, 1961-1970 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    June 17, 1961-March 1970
  - Roster of the Members-Elect of the Senate and House of Representatives (One Hundred and Ninth General Assembly of Ohio), 1971-1972 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - State Legislation - Ohio, 1966-1971 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - State Legislation - Ohio, 1961-1968 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - State Legislation - Ohio (Conveyor Belt), 1950-1958 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - State Legislation - Oklahoma, 1955-1967 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - State Legislation - Oregon, 1966-1971 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - State Legislation - Pennsylvania, 1965-1968 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - State Legislation - Rhode Island, 1939-1970 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - State Legislation - South Carolina, 1935-1966 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - State Legislation - South Dakota, 1957-1970 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - State Legislation - Tennessee, 1953-1970 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - State Legislation - Texas, 1963-1970 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - State Legislation - Utah, 1959-1969 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - State Legislation - Vermont, 1951-1970 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- 53-286-0 (Box 108)
  - State Legislation - Virginia, 1962-1968 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - State Legislation - Washington, 1955-1967 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - State Legislation - West Virginia, 1963-1970 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - State Legislation - Wisconsin, 1959-1967 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - State Legislation - Wyoming, 1962-1971 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Current File to Baily - Washington, District of Columbia, 1966-1967 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Cost of Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks (BRAC) on Sale of Homes on Staff Employees Moving to Rosemont, Illinois, 1969-1970 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Transportation Communication Union - Cost Moving to Rosemont, Illinois, 1969-1971 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Expense Accounts - Bell Telephone Credit Cards, 1965-1970 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Expense Accounts, 1970-1971 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    August 1970-January 1971
  - Transportation Communication Union - Expense Accounts, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Not Moving to Rosemont Illinois, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Expenses - Moving to Rosemont, Illinois, 1969-1970 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Expense Accounts, 1968-1970 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    January 1968-July 1970
  - Expense Accounts - 1970 Election Campaign (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Expense Accounts - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    January-June 1970
  - Expense Accounts - Staff and Others (Bishop-McGuire), 1970 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    July-December 1970
  - Expense Accounts - Staff and Others (Mayberry-Wilson), 1970 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - Expense Accounts - General, 1966-1967 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Office Expenses, 1966-1969 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    1966-June 30, 1969
  - Office Expenses - Washington, 1969-1970 (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - Office Expenses (L.E. Dennis), 1966-1967 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    June 1966-June 1967
  - Expenses - Holiday International, Incorporated: M. Galen and H. Manushaw, 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- 286 - 0-2 (Box 109)
  - Expenses - Holiday International Incorporated: M. Galen and H. Manushaw, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Office Expenses, 1961-1969 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Expenses - Zel E. Lipsen, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Expenses - John Gonella, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    October 16-20, 1969
  - Expenses - Lewis Gray and Associates, 1967-1970 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Expense Accounts - International Vice Presidents, 1965-1969 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Expense Accounts - Grand Lodge Organizers Representatives (Barchelder-Condo), 1958-1970 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Expense Accounts - Grand Lodge Organizers Representatives (Bernard-Dickinson), 1958-1970 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Expense Accounts - Grand Lodge Organizers Representatives (Elliot-Lockhart), 1965-1970 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Expense Accounts - Grand Lodge Organizers Representatives (McCarthy-Mayberry), 1958-1970 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Expense Accounts - Grand Lodge Organizers Representatives (Radice-Yoneda), 1958-1970 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Expense Accounts - Grand Lodge Organizers Representatives (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Expense Account - Organizers (Bernard-Wilbur), 1970 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Expense Account - Organizers (Cooper-McCarthy), 1970 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Expense Account - Organizers (Lassel-McCauley), 1970 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- 2-297-2 (Box 110)
  - Expense Accounts - Board of Trustees, 1944-1969 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Expense Accounts - International President, 1924-1968 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Judi Laws, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - L.G. Melton - Texas Voter Registration, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - John Allen Cross, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Earl Quinn, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Frank Parra, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Donald Ray Harkins, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Bruce Pike, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Expenses Accounts - Harold L. Crosier, HR 13300, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - James T. Mular, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Peter McGuire, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - L.J. Rancourt, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - J.P. Trainor, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - J.J. Kennedy, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Expense Accounts - Advances to Grand Lodge Employees, 1965-1968 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    July 1965-December 1968
  - Expense Accounts - Advances to Grand Lodge Employees, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Expense Accounts - Advances to Grand Lodge Employees (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (L.F. Batory), 1967-1969 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Robert L. Bryson, 1970-1971 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (E. Courtney), 1957-1969 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (K. Lasocki), 1967-1969 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - M. L. McAllister, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    March 24 and 29, 1971
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Special Representatives - Activities (R.J. McCarthy), 1964-1971 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - George Kern, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    June 26, 1970
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (J. Maka), 1964-1971 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (P.P. Masson), 1959-1970 (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (William Pye), 1972 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (Charles Turner), 1968-1969 (Box 110, Folder 29)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (C.R. Young), 1973 (Box 110, Folder 30)
    October 1973
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (C.R. Young), 1972-1973 (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (H.L. Walker), 1973 (Box 110, Folder 32)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President, 1971-1975 (Box 110, Folder 33)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (R.B. Pike), 1971-1974 (Box 110, Folder 34)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (J.C. Fletcher), 1971-1975 (Box 110, Folder 35)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (D.A. Bobo), 1972-1974 (Box 110, Folder 36)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Vice Presidents (L.E. Dennis), 1974 (Box 110, Folder 37)
  - Grand Lodge Officers (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 110, Folder 38)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Taxes, 1968-1969 (Box 110, Folder 39)
  - H.J. Batchelder, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 40)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (Benjamin H. Clegg), 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 41)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (C.B. Bailey), 1960-1967 (Box 110, Folder 42)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice Presidents (General), 1969-1972 (Box 110, Folder 43)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help and Furniture (C.L. Dennis), 1969 (Box 110, Folder 44)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (L.E. Dennis), 1969 (Box 110, Folder 45)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (J.D. Bearden), 1963-1971 (Box 110, Folder 46)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (R.L. Bryson), 1969 (Box 110, Folder 47)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (M. Calligaris), 1966 (Box 110, Folder 48)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (W.R. Clark), 1967-1970 (Box 110, Folder 49)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (D.K. Campbell), 1958-1968 (Box 110, Folder 50)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (P.T. Clancy), 1958-1969 (Box 110, Folder 51)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (W.J. Dickinson), 1963-1969 (Box 110, Folder 52)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (Kenneth L. Elliot), 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 53)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (P. Erkiletian), 1960-1970 (Box 110, Folder 54)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (L.H. Freeman), 1971-1972 (Box 110, Folder 55)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (W.H. Grant), 1963-1969 (Box 110, Folder 56)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (J.B. Haines), 1963-1970 (Box 110, Folder 57)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (C.E. Kief), 1964-1971 (Box 110, Folder 58)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (P.B. Kingsolver), 1966-1967 (Box 110, Folder 59)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (D.A. Ligon, 1963-1970 (Box 110, Folder 60)
- 297 - 2-6 (Box 111)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (S.V.W. Loehr), 1969-1971 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (A.R. Lowry), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (M.M. Martinez), 1965-1970 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (L. McKinney), 1958-1968 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (C.B. Moore), 1965-1968 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (Sam Placksin), 1973 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (H.P. Schmidt), 1960-1966 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (A.M. Strader), 1963-1968 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (C.F. Sommerfield), 1962-1969 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (D.F. Sweeney), 1964-1971 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (J.A. Varnadoe), 1964-1969 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (H.L. Walker), 1966-1968 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - German Zambrana, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (F.J. Summerville), 1958-1969 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (F.V. Reynolds), 1964-1967 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (C.E. Robinson), 1964-1967 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (J.H. Moberly), 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (L.L. Zosel), 1962-1968 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (E.L. Roers), 1958-1969 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (K.D. Shaw), 1964-1971 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (R.M. Mayberry), 1958-1968 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (Jack F. Otero), 1969-1970 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (F.H. Hall), 1964-1968 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (Mrs. Christine Watson Plump), 1968 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (John A. Montagne), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - International Vice President (D.J. Sullivan), 1963-1968 (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Activities - Representatives and Organizers (H.L. Tuttle), 1958-1968 (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Location Report Cards, 1955-1967 (Box 111, Folder 28)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Monthly Reports, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 29)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (C.B. Bailey), 1966 (Box 111, Folder 30)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Offices, Office Help, and Furniture (Downard), 1963-1968 (Box 111, Folder 31)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (D.J. Sullivan), 1963-1970 (Box 111, Folder 32)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (C.B. Moore), 1965-1969 (Box 111, Folder 33)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (Frank Hall), 1962-1965 (Box 111, Folder 34)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (J.D. Bearden), 1959-1970 (Box 111, Folder 35)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help and Furniture (W.R. Clark), 1967 (Box 111, Folder 36)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Offices, Office Help, and Furniture (Erickson), 1957-1966 (Box 111, Folder 37)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (Tom Fitzgibbon), 1969-1971 (Box 111, Folder 38)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (J.B. Haines), 1959-1966 (Box 111, Folder 39)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (C.E. Kief), 1963-1968 (Box 111, Folder 40)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (S.V.W. Loehr), 1969-1970 (Box 111, Folder 41)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (R.J. McCarthy), 1961-1971 (Box 111, Folder 42)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (McKinney), 1960-1963 (Box 111, Folder 43)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (Genera), 1957-1971 (Box 111, Folder 44)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Offices, Office Help, and Furniture (Ligon), 1963-1970 (Box 111, Folder 45)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (K.D. Shaw), 1957-1970 (Box 111, Folder 46)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (N.C.R. Offices - Detroit), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 47)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (C.L. Dennis), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 48)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (W.J. Ryan), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 49)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (W.A. Schults), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 50)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (A.B. Seward), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 51)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Office, Office Help, and Furniture (Tool-Die and Mold Makers Guild), 1969 (Box 111, Folder 52)
- 7-298-50 (Box 112)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Moving Expenses, 1962-1971 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Moving Expenses (Fernstrom), 1968 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Moving Expenses (Patrolmen), 1969 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Moving Expenses (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Organizers' Salaries, 1964-1970 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Sick Leave (Bernard-Clark), 1958-1969 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Sick Leave (Grant-Leroux), 1964-1967 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - M. Martinez, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Weekly Reports, 1964-1972 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    January 1964-September 1972
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Sick Leave (Maxa-McCarthy), 1958-1968 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Sick Leave (Reynolds-Tuttle), 1958-1968 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Sick Leave (Varnadoe), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Sick Leave (Dickinson-Erkiletian), 1958-1969 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Investments - Grand Lodge Funds, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    Includes Kodak prints
  - Auditing Grand Lodge Accounts (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Amended Actuarial Report on the Cost of Including Officers and Employees of the Transportation-Communication Employees Union under the Railway Clerks Staff Retirement Plan, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    March 20, 1970
  - Grand Lodge - Passwords, 1926-1966 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Staff Retirement, 1971 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    March-December 1971
  - Staff Retirement, 1969-1972 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    November 1969-June 23, 1972
  - Staff Retirement, 1970-1971 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    May 1970-February 28, 1971
- 50-55 (Box 113)
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Weekly Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    October 1972-March 1973
  - Grand Lodge Officers - Reports (Weekly and Bimonthly), 1973 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    April-September 1973: Weekly Reports. September 1973-December 4, 1973: Bimonthly Reports
  - Grand Lodge - Group Life Insurance (Officers and Employees): American General Life Insurance Company, Policy 5555, 1973-1974 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    January 1973-May 1974
  - Health and Welfare - Travelers Policy GA-23111, 1973-1974 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    June 1973-May 1974
  - Grand Lodge - Group Hospital Travelers Policy GA-23111, 1974-1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    June 1974-June 1976
  - Health and Welfare - Travelers Policy GA-23111, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    January 1972-May 1973
  - Grand Lodge - Legal Department, 1965-1973 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Staff Retirement - Claims, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- 52-8-59 (Box 114)
  - Liability Personal Automobiles, 1967-1968 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Liability - Personal Automobiles (Insurance Requirements for Mileage Allowance for Personally Owned Automobiles), 1964-1969 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Grand Lodge - Group Insurance, Officers and Employees (Reports to Office of Labor Management and Welfare Pension), 1962-1969 (Box 114, Folder 3)